here's an interesting chaos game variant
start with these two matrices A and B
and consider the apine linear
Transformations ax and BX
-5.5 these two Transformations are
applied to the plane and shown here
start with a point in the plane and
apply both Transformations choose one of
the two output points at random Say by
flipping a coin and apply both
Transformations again then repeat this
process each time select one of the
output points at random and apply both
Transformations let's do this 25,000
times to see what the resulting shape is
no matter the starting point or the
outcome of the random coin flips along
the way the limiting shape will always
look like this the resulting fractal
shape is called the levy C curve or the
levy Dragon it can be generated in other
ways but this is how we generate it
using an iterated function system